<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Dialogue>
  <Sentences>
    <Sentence character="Percy White" string="An embroidered handkerchief with initials E.B. was found very close to the stage where your father was found dead. Can you tell me if it belongs to you, and if it’s the case, why was it there?"></Sentence>
    <Sentence character="Elizabeth Blayton" string="Ah… I prefer not to speak about this detective."></Sentence>
    <Sentence character="Percy White" string="Ms. Blayton, it’s not like if you had the choice. We found an evidence revealing that you were on the crime scene, placing you as the main suspect. So you will tell me why, now."></Sentence>
    <Sentence character="Elizabeth Blayton" string="If you insist detective… But don’t say anything to my brother, I beg you."></Sentence>
    <Sentence character="Percy White" string="It will be our secret Ms. Blayton."></Sentence>
    <Sentence character="Elizabeth Blayton" string="The handkerchief is mine indeed. As you may know, the relationship between my father and my brother isn’t the one a father and his son should have, and this has been for several years now. Robert had to assume our father’s responsibilities and took care of our mother and me, he gave me everything and made me who I am now. Because of our father’s behaviour, he forbade me to see him again. I haven’t seen my father since many years now. I’ve been trying to find him for a couple of weeks now, which was rather easy given his renown. As soon as I was told he was coming to London for a series of representations, I thought it was an opportunity for me to go and meet him so that he gives me an explanation. On Saturday I decided to go to the theatre, he was rehearsing his role. I discreetly slipped into the theatre and hid behind a curtain to watch him, but I was not able to go and talk to him at that moment. Then I saw his odious behaviour towards the other actors and the technical team, which revives me his absence when I was a child, and how he badly treated my mother and my brother the very short time he was at home. Past rose to the surface. I simply burst into tears. I was paralysed, then after a short time I ran away the fastest as I can to escape this place, and go far away from this man. This is the moment I probably lost my handkerchief, everything was so sudden… Once again Detective White, promise me you won’t talk to Robert about this, it would devastate him."></Sentence>
    <Sentence character="Percy White" string="I give you my word Ms. Blayton. Thank you very much for your testimony, I guess it wasn’t easy for you to live."></Sentence>
  </Sentences>
</Dialogue>